{"test_questions": [[{"question": "If a designer is developing a plan for a project in which the entire part is made out of \u00be\" thick plywood and he only wants to use one view, he should use the ________ view.", "opta": "front", "optb": "top", "optc": "right", "optd": "back", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In developing a multi-view drawing the drafter can use a ________ line to help locate the top and right side views.", "opta": "object", "optb": "hidden", "optc": "dimension", "optd": "miter", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The type of line that projects from an object for the express purpose of locating a dimension is a ________ line.", "opta": "visible", "optb": "hidden", "optc": "extension", "optd": "dimension", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Center lines are used to locate or represent the centers of ________.", "opta": "arcs", "optb": "circles", "optc": "hidden round features", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Architectural drawings used to construct a house are often plotted with a scale of \u00bc\" = 1'-0\". What scale is this?", "opta": "Quarter", "optb": "Half", "optc": "Full", "optd": "Double", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In multi-view drawing it is common practice to include three views, the front, the top and the right side. If no dimensions are required on the right side view the drafter can ________.", "opta": "leave the view as is", "optb": "eliminate the view", "optc": "use the left view instead", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The AutoCAD command used to combine two or more primitive shapes into a single complex 3-dimensional model is ________.", "opta": "add", "optb": "union", "optc": "attach", "optd": "form", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Most architectural drawings produced for field use by building contractors are printed on architectural \"D\" size paper which measures ________.", "opta": "24\" X 36\"", "optb": "18\" X 24\"", "optc": "11\" X 17\"", "optd": "34\" X 22\"", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Geometric primitives include shapes such as ________.", "opta": "boxes", "optb": "cylinders", "optc": "wedges", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A full scale technical drawing will have a scale factor of ________.", "opta": "1:1", "optb": "1:2", "optc": "2:1", "optd": "1:4", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}